You didn't know already?
I'm saying that
some of the humans are unique,
by which I mean that they're practically
overflowing with life energy.
We're calling them Rares
because they're quite difficult to find.
[Turtle Ant] Difficult, you say?
[Rammot] What trick is this?
They seem to have gotten stronger
all of a sudden.
[Killua] Thunderbolt!
[Rammot screams]
[Kite] If you wanna get stronger,
this is a perfect opportunity,
but if you aren't prepared,
you won't be able to endure the ordeal.
From here on out,
in victory or defeat, it'll be hell.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
KITE X AND X SLOTS
[narrator] Kite, Gon, and Killua
have advanced deep within the NGL
in search of the Chimera Ant nest,
and have now arrived at a cliff
with peculiar openings.
Is this the place
where the Chimera Ants nest?
No, it's not.
so don't let your guard down.
The pill's called DD
and is mass-produced right here.
The hottest new drug on the mainland.
It's made from bira trees.
There must be a field close by.
Ironic, given their status
as conservationists, right?
They're making more than just drugs. Look.
They're the same ones from earlier.
[Kite] If I had to hazard a guess,
I'd say only the leaders of the NGL
know the truth.
The other community members
probably genuinely identify
with the environmental message.
This facility, it's the core
of the NGL underground, isn't it?
and that a bunch of amateurs with guns
didn't stand a chance against them.
But what about their boss?
He either escaped or was eaten.
Either way this is bad news.
[Kite] They're slowly approaching
through the middle tunnel.
There are more in the left and right.
-Everything within 45 meters.
-[gasps] Did you say 45?
Depending on my mental and physical state,
I'm able to increase that by a few meters.
Here they come.
[scraping]
[whimpering]
[both gasp]
[men whimpering]
Keep it down, you two.
[men gagging]
Hmm?
Who the hell are you?
How dare you intrude on my turf?
Help us. You gotta help us.
Shut your damn mouth, Spot.
You're a dog, remember?
[gasps]
[chuckling] Oops.
I didn't mean to do that.
[man whimpers]
[panting]
No, don't!
-Let me go.
-Don't move carelessly.
There's more than one enemy here,
and they want you to rush toward them.
[boys gasp]
[laughing]
Now, bye-bye.
[whimpers]
Help me.
They've always been aggressive,
but consuming malicious humans
has had an effect on them,
and it's made them even more evil.
Huh? What do you mean?
Phagogenesis, right?
If we don't deal with them here,
there's no telling
how many more people will be killed.
Go, capture them.
I'll take the one in the back.
The ones rushing at us will go to you two.
Okay, we got it.
[Kite] Don't hesitate. Fight to kill.
[boys] Bring it!
-[grunting]
-[screeching]
[cackling]
Now, this next one is just for you.
My unblockable thousand-hand fist.
[shouts]
[screams]
Hmm. That sure was a close one.
You have a lot more power
than I was expecting.
[Gon] Damn, these guys are tough.
They have the hard shells of insects,
combined with the agility of humans.
Hmm, I wonder what's running
through your mind right now.
-[Gon] He's right.
-Huh?
I can't hesitate.
Now, show me rock!
[Killua] Don't hesitate, kill.
[laughing]
[Killua] Been a while
since I flipped my switch on.
[Mosquito Ant screeches]
SERPENT WORK
You!
[laughs] You pathetic little fool.
This is my real stinger.
[groans softly]
Well, how does it feel as the poison
spreads through your body? Feel good?
Hmm, works like a charm.
Once I get him addicted,
we'll have another human dog.
Are you done over there?
Oh, guess not.
[neck cracks]
But how?
Yeah. Poison doesn't work on me, sorry.
Oh, I see.
-If you behave, I'll make this quick.
-Oh, well.
[body thudding]
[scoffs] Can't believe
she fell for a cheap trick.
[Centipede] What is this power
overflowing from his body?
Any closer,
and I could get seriously injured, but…
The source of his power is in his fist.
Or maybe he'll pull his punch
and use a kick.
No, he's definitely going to use his fist.
then I can bite him and inject my venom.
Let's run a little simulation.
[grunts]
[yelling]
[Centipede] Yes, it'll work.
It's just a punch.
No matter how strong it is,
I can take it as long as I'm prepared.
[Yunju] Hey, we should
get this started soon, huh?
-Wait a little longer.
-Screw that!
It's not like you have a choice anyway.
[sighs]
Now, let me see what you've got.
If you insist.
[Yunju] Huh? This is my castle.
A king doesn't need to have a reason
to be in his own castle.
I would expect
you'd want to avoid this place.
-Huh?
-He should be here.
Beats me. I figure he's probably
already inside the queen's belly.
who likes to amuse himself
by making humans into dogs.
[laughs] Is that so?
Well, you're right,
I can't wait to strip you down,
and put a collar around your neck.
[grunts]
Bastard.
[growls]
[Yunju yells]
[grunts, groans]
Damn it! [grunts]
[Crazy Slots] You know what
your problem is? You're too impatient.
[mimics whirring]
Are you messing with me?
Forget about making you my dog,
I'm going to kill you.
-Four.
-Really? That's a bad spin.
What did you just say?
I don't have any bad spins,
ungrateful bastard.
You're dead!
[thudding]
[grunting]
[Centipede] I'm gonna pretend
to attack him while I block his punch,
and then, when his guard is down,
I'll just grab him up and take a bite.
Here goes.
[yelling]
Janken…
[Centipede] Just like I thought. Block!
Impossible! Where the hell
was he hiding that thing?
[Kite] Don't relax,
even after dismembering them.
You have to stay vigilant.
Remember, the head and body
can survive for an entire day
after they've been separated.
No matter what, destroy the head.
And whenever you kill one, if you can,
make sure you do it quietly and quickly.
[cackling]
I'm the great mad clown
known as Crazy Slots.
Don't ever forget that, okay?
-[Kite] Just leave already.
-[Crazy Slots gasps]
[Killua] What a weird power.
-So it talks on its own?
-Pretty much.
Since it's a roulette wheel,
does that mean you don't get to choose
what weapon you get?
Right.
Sadly, once I get one, I'm not allowed to
exchange it for another, no matter what.
I'm stuck. [sighs]
[wing blowing]
It appears that we've lost the signal
from Yunju's team.
[Leol] Were they killed?
The signal indicated three enemies,
and that they looked tastier
than the others.
So tasty that I just can't believe it.
Yum-yum. [slurps]
[Leol] So they must be
the Rares. [chuckles]
Now we have a reason to go.
Yunju was using the factory as his base?
[Flutter] He was, so I'm sure the rare
humans will still be near the facility.
Oh, yay! I love feasts.
[Kite] As you saw, both of your powers
are significantly easier to use than mine.
You're not kidding.
Anything's easier than that.
Yeah.
[Kite] Gon, you seem to have incorporated
enhancer, transmuter and emitter abilities
into your rock, paper, scissors.
You'll have ample opportunity to improve.
Let's hurry, the nest is close.
I don't know what's happening, but…
[breathing heavily]
[laughs]
My body, it's overflowing with energy.
What in the hell is all this, huh?
[Peggy] What's the matter, Colt?
A signal from a soldier.
Rammot is acting strangely.
[Peggy] In what way?
I've never witnessed
such ferocious life energy.
[continues laughing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Inspiration To Evolve".
I want inspiration to evolve.
[Killua] Okay, but when will you?
[Gon and Killua] Now, of course.